# **Ariel Campos**

337-342-5749 | ariel.campos@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/arielcamposstl/

## **Areas of Expertise**

<ul> <li>□ Technical writing/documentation</li> <li>□ Windows Server administration</li> <li>□ C#</li> <li>□ Linux system administration</li> <li>□ ITIL process</li> <li>□ Active Directory</li> </ul>	<ul> <li>□ Incident management</li> <li>□ SQL</li> <li>□ Python</li> <li>□ HTML/CSS</li> <li>□ Solarwinds</li> <li>□ ServiceNow</li> </ul>	
Technica aunchcode, St. Louis, Missouri	al Experience	
C101 graduate(Full Stack Development tr	• ,	
Coursework: Python	<b>Projects:</b> □ Multi-user blog υ	
i yulon	- Mail asci blog	ıcina
SQL database queries	Pvthon/Flask/Jinia2/SQLAlchemv st	ısing ack
SQL database queries HTML/CSS	Python/Flask/Jinja2/SQLAlchemy st  Web item and collection database u	ack

### **Professional Experience**

#### ShipWorks, St. Louis, Missouri Technical Support Representative

2018 - Present

- Assist customers in troubleshooting the ShipWorks software, both over the phone and via remote access session
- Create and update support tickets with the Oracle RightNow ticketing system
- □ Create and edit label, invoice, and report templates using XML and CSS stylesheets
- Work with customer's order databases through database management software and by running SQL queries
- □ Import and troubleshoot connections to store databases through the ODBC interface

#### Jolt Technology, LLC/Technology Partners, Chesterfield/Ballwin, Missouri 2017 - 2018 Client Helpdesk Analyst

- Open service tickets and assist clients with basic troubleshooting, escalate to application support if needed, strictly adhering to a 5 minute first response time
- Administer domain-level Windows networks through Active Directory and other system administration tools
- Manage and administer company-wide Office365 licensing, installation, and troubleshooting
- Monitor and remote access via the Solarwinds NCentral managed services platform
- Update and create tickets via the Zendesk support portal

#### Thomson Reuters, St. Louis, Missouri Associate Application Support Engineer

2014 - 2017

- Provide first-level technical support/delivery capability in a technical area for the flagship financial data infrastructure of Thomson Reuters
- □ Monitor server health and alarm messages via an array of IBM Tivoli/Netcool views and

# **Ariel Campos**

337-342-5749 | ariel.campos@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/arielcamposstl/

raise and investigate support tickets with other teams in SM9, JIRA, and ServiceNow

- Work with both tech ops and other teams to investigate, document, and escalate tickets in a timely and informative manner
- Document and write regular major incident notification updates for for publishing to stakeholder clients
- Work with datacenter, netcoms, and hardware vendors to augment and complete incident investigation and troubleshooting

# AT&T Mobility, Rantoul, IL Customer Service Representative

2012 - 2014

Assist customers with billing issues and basic troubleshooting

#### Richland Community College, Decatur, Illinois Library Technical Assistant for Cataloging

2009 - 2012

 Assisted with patron technical and research questions, copy cataloged new items into the collection, corrected any cataloging errors with the records in the collection

#### Education

Launchcode, St. Louis, Missouri

2018-Present

University of Missouri-Rolla/Missouri University of Science and Technology, Rolla, Missouri 2001 - 2007

**BA History/Education**